Light a fire
Fire it up
Work it up
Hey kids! How are you?
All good?
- All good
You didn't even greet me, Raees
Got down straight to work, eh?
- Greetings!
Greetings!
Who gathered the most today?
- We brought you the entire market
First-class!
Hey, add some more chemical here
Gujarat
A State in Independent India
where every day is a 'dry day'
Dry day means no trading of liquor
The penalty for selling liquor
is ten years imprisonment
However, prohibition begets rebellion
Even today Gujarat is considered
a liquor-free State
Yet, illegal liquor worth 250 billion
is sold here every year
This would've been impossible
if it weren't for Raees
Take a bath, Raees
From Umbergaon to Kutch,
the longest coastline of India
stretching 1600 kilometres
is part of our Gujarat
Raees, you read
Read!
Gujarat...
In the north of Gujarat...
- Come here
I don't want to,
but you boys compel me to beat you
Hush
Read now
D
P
R.
- Very good
Step down, son
Nothing to worry, Aminaben
Raees' eyesight is weak.
He just needs glasses
I hope it's not urgent...?
Ammi, I won't go to school
without glasses
Relax.
- Why?
Is it a new idea to bunk school?
For his weak eyesight,
the kid is quite sharp
I can't see what's written on the board.
Miss Ratna beats me
What are you saying?
She hits my tiger?
How much will it cost?
Don't worry about the money, Aminaben
You can pay me later
No, doctor. I don't want him
to have a borrowed vision,
but a clear one
We'll get it done in a few days
If I sense trouble,
I'll holler 'Bhaijaan'
That's your cue
Make it fast
Bhaijaan!
- Hey!
Who's there?
Are you stealing the spectacles?
Bhaijaan!
Are you stealing the glasses?
Stop, you thief!
- Hail Gandhiji!
Stop!
Idiot.
Where did you get this frame from?
From Gandhiji.
- Gandhiji?
It won't work
Nope
Why don't you come tomorrow?
I'll make real glasses for you.
Go on
I have no money
No money?
2 rupees fees is a must
Rule is rule, no?
Take it and make the payment.
Problem solved
Give me five!
Go on...
hey, idiot
Come back here
Give Gandhiji back his frame
He needs it more
Go on
It's awesome, Sadiq.
Just like binoculars!
Look! Gandhiji is smiling
Qasim is cleaning the car
Chakor is inflating the tyres
Look! The cops are
going to raid Ilyas' liquor den
Our business is in danger, Sadiq.
Let's hurry
Jamil, clean it up.
Clear everything
Boxes, bottles... hide everything!
Leave nothing outside!
Hurry up!
Quick!
No one escapes!
- Greetings!
Spread out!
- Not again!
Find out where he's hidden the liquor!
- Are you looking for some treasure?
Check the sacks!
- There's nothing, sir
Open it!
- What are you looking for?
Hurry up! Search well.
Anything there?
You!
Come here
You like to whistle, eh?
Shall I make you whistle?
What say?
Hey!
Why did you slap him?
- Ask him
Ask him why I slapped him
What's inside? What is it?
Goods. It's my business.
- Goods?
Or, is it fodder for riots?
It is a ruse
for your shady business, isn't it?
Being a cop is your job,
selling scrap is my business
Get this loud and clear
For us, no business is small
And no faith
is greater than business
140 people died in Fatehpura last night
after drinking spurious liquor
Police arrested Ilyas, a bootlegger
Is it true that no business is small?
And no faith greater than business?
It's true
As long as it doesn't harm anyone
Get that?
Sleep
Speak up, buddy.
What's the plan?
How do we earn now?
- We'll sell liquor
Fool. Ilyas is in jail.
Do you also plan to go?
The cops arrest those who sell hooch,
not imported liquor
So?
We'll work for Jairaj Seth
He sells imported liquor
It's difficult, Amit
But I'll give it one last try for you
Bye.
Chandu!
What's the problem?
Seth, roadblocks are set up everywhere.
Delivery is impossible today
Amit called thrice...
- What if I deliver?
Who's he?
- Both of them used to work for Ilyas
Six bottles
Can you deliver?
I'll take 3 bucks per bottle.
- Hey, Four-eyes
Are you trying to extort?
- Hey!
Don't you call me Four-eyes!
- For those thick glasses,
what else do I call you, Four-eyes?
- I told you not to call me Four-eyes!
Freaking Four-eyes!
Deal
3 rupees per bottle
Hey, give me the bottles
Never call me Four-eyes!
Get that?
Where to?
- I live here
Show me your licence.
- It's at home
Check his licence
Want to check, sir?
- Beat it!
Employ the boy from tomorrow
He's as shrewd as a merchant
and as fearless as a warrior
Greetings, Seth
Sadiq, the cops are causing trouble
at Narol Chowkdi
Tell Raees to get the consignment cleared.
- I'll see to it
Down!
Up!
What's so funny?
Here's your cut
Release the stuff
That settles it.
Move it
Let it go!
- Well,
it isn't settled yet
What's up, bro?
Come over here
Your pockets were empty,
I filled them. - Right
You gave me a flat,
now fix it
That'll settle it
How can I fix it?
- Inflate it
How can I?
Blow into it. C'mon!
Do it!
Be ethical in business.
It saves time and honour
Blow it
We unload his stuff,
we manage his warehouses
and he takes all the profit!
Get some onions
How long are we
to work our tails off for Jairaj?
Let's set up our own business
We are not cut out for business
Enjoy the bird in hand
We are Gujaratis.
Business runs in our blood
In this business, we need backing,
not blood
Not backing
Guts
You forgot Jairaj's words
As fearless as a warrior,
as shrewd as a merchant
I've got it all
I'll win this one too, Ujjwalbhai
Take a look now, Ramnikbhai.
- I'll go one more round blind
I'll check mine.
- Greetings, Seth
Greetings
You bring me good luck, my Ace
You're funny, Seth
Not aces
We're mere servants
My tiger's not in the mood
What's wrong?
Seth, I've been working for
years under you
I want to set up my own business now
Business, why?
I'll hike your salary
Enjoy
Sadiq, reason with him
I tried, Seth
He's made up his mind.
He won't give up
Really?
Come on
My boy has grown up.
- No, Seth
He'll set up his own business.
- It's not like that
So you must've decided about
vendors and distribution
You are here.
How can I even think of other vendors?
You know, in our business,
you have to spend money
like a drunken sailor
I hope you are cash rich?
- What are you saying, Ramnikbhai?
Obviously, he has the money
Sadiq?
He has the money, right?
How much stuff do you need?
Worth 400,000 rupees?
300,000?
200,000?
Raees, how much do I give you?
Seth...
just... worth 100,000
Never mind
Pay the money, take the stuff
Seth, I don't have the money now
I need some time
Not even 100,000?
He doesn't have the money.
He needs time
You have worked for me
all these years... I'll give it to you
Three days
Give me cash in three days
and take the stuff
Fine?
72 hours
Else, you get zilch!
Keep it
The clock will keep ticking
Your turn
Why did you shoot your mouth off?
If we don't pay up in three days,
Jairaj will destroy us, you know that
Greetings, Raees.
- Greetings, Qasimbhai
The car's a cracker!
It costs 100,000. Want to buy?
Forget it.
This motorbike is fine with me
Try it once. It rides like a plane!
Next time. Bye.
Move it!
God keep you
Hey!
- Careful!
You'd have killed it!
Who will compensate for it?
- Lallan, you idiot!
He's not even hurt!
- What if he was hurt?
Would you pay me 500?
- 500 rupees?
I'll buy his entire family for 500!
It's the time of Eid.
I bought it for 300
It won't sell below 500 to 1000 here.
You know that?
Move it, Lallan
Don't mess my brains!
Is he going to build a castle out of it?
Hey... where do you think you are going?
Where to? Tell me...
Raees, you're back so soon?
My mind just worked up a miracle
Let's see what your car's got
Sadiq, hop in
Give me the keys, Qasim
Take care.
Drive only till the square and back
It's a car, not a date
Relax. I'm leaving my motorbike behind.
Hop in
Careful
Raees
Hey, speak up. What's the plan?
You bartered your motorbike for the car,
and now the car for the goats
Are you setting up a slaughterhouse?
As Lallan said, it's Eid
People even pay 1000 for a goat.
- 1000?
Who will pay 1000 here in Fatehpura?
Not in Fatehpura but in Mumbai
We're going to Mumbai?!
We have to pay 100,000 to Jairaj
in three days. Do you have a better plan?
Do you have one?
Ask him
Excuse me.
Where can we set up shop?
Over there.
- Up ahead
Herd them ahead.
- Move
Over there
Greetings.
- Greetings
Can we set up shop in the corner?
Whose goats are they?
- Mine
Do you have the permission?
Permission...? No
Where have you come from?
From Gujarat
Pick up your goats and get lost.
Beat it
We'll set up by the corner
Hey! Don't you get it?
Brother, it's Eid
We'll also make some money.
You'll have our blessings
If we slaughter you along with the goats,
we'll be blessed
Raees, it's not our territory. Come on.
- Hey, Four-eyes!
Can't you hear?
Get out of here!
Darn!
- Four-eyes needs a hearing-aid now!
Hey, Four-eyes!
Never call me Four-eyes!
Of all the people,
you had to mess with Musabhai
If you sensed trouble,
why didn't you holler 'Bhaijaan'?
It'd have alerted me.
- You hardly gave me time
You just whacked him
Was I at fault?
All right, my mistake.
You passed out in one blow!
Let's go. Musa is waiting
Man is always accompanied
by an angel and the devil
Anger is evil
because it's the devil's forte
Your boys started it
We were here to do business
Your goats made for great biryani
What have you to sell now?
A goat is a lion's prey,
not business
Well,
no business is small
And no faith
is greater than any business
My mother taught me
My loss is great,
and I have little time to compensate
I have a right to their blessings
If you agree, we'll take it and leave
Come here
Your glasses
It'll help you see the road ahead
Musabhai...
can we get a plate of biryani to share?
We're hungry
For all the festivities around,
we'll be observing a fast!
Forget Jairaj.
How will you repay mechanic Qasim?
What is it?
Do we look like clowns?
They made a circus out of us!
And here you are eating away!
The biryani is worth 100,000.
You should have some
I could eat a horse!
Well, you hardly took a beating.
You deserve a lesser share
Stop kidding.
They crushed my stomach
Ace, we have 3475 in all
What do I do with it?
Shall I give it to Jairaj?
Or, repay Qasim?
Ice your wounds
Creditors come knocking
even before we set up shop!
Darn, you followed us here?
Hajibhai sent me from Mumbai,
to talk business
Let him in.
Come on
Tell me
Reason for the favour?
Take Musa out
I hold nothing against Musa
And we don't kill. Right?
Listen up
If I wanted to take orders, I wouldn't
have set out to start a business
Take the money and scoot.
Move it
Musa sent it for you
He told us to kill Musa,
and now he says he's Musa's man
Who are you?
The name's Nawab
I'm Musa's Man Friday
You could've given it to me
in the train
Sure
But Musa likes to test the waters
Raees, don't take the money!
In trying to smite Jairaj, don't walk
into a deathtrap. - It's not a loan
It's for your goats.
- Raees!
Musa liked your philosophy
about business and faith
Raees!
No one can harm those
who Musa favours
What if we had agreed
to bump off Musa?
My left hand never misses its mark
Goodbye
Raees!
What's up?
- Jairaj Seth wants you. Your time is up
Get back to work
Tell Jairaj,
I have stopped dancing to his tunes
My time starts now!
Ammi,
I'm going to start my own business
God willing, I'll make a lot of money
But I will never let anyone
come to harm
Pray for me
Understand the business, Sadiq.
We'll buy stuff from Jairaj's vendors
and sell on the streets of Fatehpura.
- That's great
Cut the middlemen like Jairaj out!
Here now, there now!
Life is a journey
The city of my dreams traverses,
bundled in a bottle
If you have the wisdom,
patience to boot,
and a lot of guts,
you have nothing to worry
This world is fake
You have to turn crooked
to fix it
Follow your passions
push your will far enough,
and luck will shine on you
It's the spirit of business
Let me not take a step back
Help me return the favours
Repay, I must
Let me not take a step back
Help me return the favours
Help me in my endeavour, Lord
Help, Lord!
May I never break someone's heart
Never
I don't care
how the world goes by
I just listen to the call of my heart
Everyone is answerable
in life or in death
In the spirit of business!
Hi, Hasmukhbhai!
- How are you?
I'm fine.
It's an awesome party!
Hang on
Hey, gymnast!
Excuse me
Who invited you here?
Excuse me...
- Beat the drum!
Whose guest are you?
Mr Serpent?
Excuse me.
Whose guest are you?
Now, please don't point that finger!
I am Hasmukhbhai's guest.
Whose guest are you?
I am Hasmukhbhai.
- You are Hasmukhbhai?
Yes
You are Hasmukhbhai?
- That's me
Your smile proves it
Is this your party?
- Of course
So you're serving people hooch.
- Hey, duffer!
This is not hooch. It's scotch
It's scotch
Party's over
Attention
We'll have to end this party here
But we'll surely continue the party
at Gandhinagar police station
For your convenience,
we've organised transport. Fall in line
A blue police van is waiting outside.
Remember, friends,
don't push around.
And ladies go first
Have a safe journey to jail.
Thank you
The last Mughal!
You will rot in jail!
Sir, the opposition
will certainly raise this issue
Fix a meeting with Pasha.
I'll talk to him
Sir
What took you so long?
Sorry, sir.
Bobby was having breakfast
Let him go
I can't. She's quite flirty
Who are you talking about?
Bobby, my doggy
Not Bobby! I'm talking
about Hasmukhbhai and his party
Sir, give me a paper
Please, sir
What's this?
- Paper and pen
I can see that
Give me in writing what you just said.
I'll release him right away
What? In writing?
It's an order, Majmudar.
Release them
Sir, my name
is Jaideep Ambalal Majmudar
Ambalal is my late father
Even if his spirit asks me to release
Hasmukhbhai and his party,
I'll take it in writing.
And you are merely...!
Give it in writing, I'll release them
You'll surely get it in writing.
Your transfer orders!
Get out
Transfer him to Fatehpura.
He'll come to his senses
Come on, bowl.
- Bowl him out, Sadiq!
Come on.
- You are out!
Shot!
Six!
Go, get the ball, Sadiq
Should I go? Sure?
- Forget it
I hit it, I'll get it
Of course, you will go!
- Freaking actor
What's so funny?
Shut up!
No big deal. It's only a ball
Her father will open the door
I bet. Aasiya will open it
God help him
He hit bull's-eye
Ball?
- Yes
Not again
I warned Sadiq not to hit here
but he is incorrigible
He always hits sixers
and sends me to fetch the ball
I didn't. It was him
Raees
The stairs.
- Where?
Ah, right where they are
I love you
I see no one but you around
I have so much to say
Let me pour out my feelings now
I love you
Beautiful!
Really?
Not you
Actress Sridevi
Why do you always beat about the bush?
I can't help it.
When you smile,
it strikes me dumb!
And I just feel
like watching you!
Then take me to Our World
God willing!
When I make Our World,
you will be the first one to see it
And yes,
you will have a say out there
But my love will rule
Amazing
My love, right?
- Nope
Our World
Will you be with me?
Always!
Devji
Sir?
Sir
Will you do me a favour?
- Tell me, sir
Will you get some soda,
ice and accompaniments?
Sure, sir.
- Please
Listen.
- Yes, sir?
Forget it. It'll be difficult for you
to organise it
I got it. I will organise it, sir
What do you want?
Beer? Vodka? Rum? Whiskey?
- Whose?
Jairaj's? Ramnik's? Ujjwal's?
Or... what's the name
of the guy with glasses?
Raees?
- Right. Raees
Write.
- Sir
What do I write, sir?
- Resignation letter
Write the locations of the liquor depots
or your resignation
Write
Sorry, sir
My mistake.
- Well, Devji,
one bottle won't make a difference
Get me an entire truckload.
- Okay, sir
Whose truck is it?
- Jairaj Seth's consignment
Kodnani has got his cut
Sir, this truck is loaded with liquor
Park the truck
You've got your truckload, sir.
Now?
Call the media. Let's party
Sir!
Cards, darn it!
I've been nurturing the cops
from the lower ranks to the higher ups
for donkey's years
Still, my stuff gets bulldozed
Find out who did this!
Majmudar ruined Jairaj
A sword seeks nothing but a head
Majmudar has tasted blood
It was Jairaj's stuff,
soon it will be ours
Don't take him lightly.
A huge consignment is due
Raees
Inspector Majmudar wants to see Raees
You look different in the picture, sir
Well, they say I'm quite photogenic
You know whose consignment it was?
Jairaj's
You worked for him, didn't you?
I used to. I quit
What do you do now?
Business
What you call business
is actually crime
Come on, sir.
- Come on, sir!
Make two halves
Go on.
- We have information, sir
Raees' truck is arriving from Kalol.
- I see
The truck number is GAF 1722
Okay
Oh
Tea from a cop station.
Get used to it
You'd better shut shop
Or, I'll make it difficult for you
to even breathe
The air of Gujarat
is replete with business
You can stop me from breathing
Can you stop the air?
At this rate,
you will soon run into trouble
Get that?
Leave
Thanks for the half teacup, sir
Our truck won't arrive tomorrow
But our consignment will surely reach
Consignment will arrive
without the truck. In what?
In this.
- In a cup?
Assume that the teapot is the truck
and the cups are vehicles
Once our truck is on the highway,
Rasool will reach with four vehicles
We'll transfer the stuff to our vehicles
Then the vehicles will spread out
and enter the city via different routes
And Majmudar will be left waiting eagerly
for the truck
It's hot!
- While we receive the delivery!
Stop!
Check the truck.
- Get in
Check inside.
- Open it!
Quick!
Devji.
- Sir?
Tea time
"Your beauty, mesmerising"
"The entire neighbourhood
is crazy for you"
Get lost, wastrels!
One slap will put you in your place!
Oh, my!
At least she'll touch my cheek!
Father's down with cough again
Greetings, doctor.
- Greetings
Something's wrong with my eyes
It's you!
You forgot the rule?
It hurts badly.
Please examine me too
Capital N and capital O
That means...?
- NO
If you understand that,
why do you barge in every time?
Don't jump the queue.
Go, get out
Move.
- All right, I'll wait
Go on, collect the medicines
Okay
And send the duffer in
Yes, dear
Here you are
You are next
Really?
At the doctor's, I mean
Duffer
Number
Give him these pills after meals
Thank you
Hello, sir.
- Who are they, Devji?
Petty criminals, sir.
They are out on parole
They can be our informers
Where did you pick up the groom from?
- Sir,
I was picked up from the wedding altar
before I could...
Before I could even say 'I do.'
- Sir, he is from Raees' area
Send them away
You come with me
Get going.
- Sir, I've done nothing
I swear, I didn't do anything
Do you know Raees?
- I don't know anyone, sir
How does he do his business?
- Sir, I really don't know anyone
All I know is that
I'm getting married today
Sir, the qadi is waiting.
If I don't get back on time,
he'll leave to perform other marriages.
- What will you do outside...
when you know nothing?
Devji!
Revoke his parole!
- Please don't send me to jail again!
Or, I'll be a bachelor all my life!
Sir, at least let me get married
Do you want to complete the rituals?
- Yes, sir
In that case, find out
where Raees hides his stuff
Do you agree?
- I do
Agree?
- I do, sir
You are married!
Off you go now
Run before the qadi takes off
Thank you, sir
We have to band together to save
the business from Majmudar, Raees
I agree
I'll be the chairman of your syndicate
Don't fly too high
Or, you'll get cut
If I was scared of getting cut,
I wouldn't fly kites
I'd hold spools
Gotcha!
He got him!
Raees, have you forgotten
Jairaj's favours?
I remember the favours.
Right, Sadiq?
He had given us three days
I give you three weeks.
Think over it
I'll be the chairman
of the syndicate, nevertheless
Hang on
Catch
The clock will be ticking
Pull!
You cut the wrong kite
You goofed up!
Darn!
It soars higher and higher
The heart soars higher and higher
like a kite
It soars higher and higher
The heart soars higher and higher
like a kite
It's just a game, so to speak
Yet, my heart takes flight like a kite,
whilst those eyes are as sharp as a string
Tied to the kite is a string's destiny
It soars higher and higher
The heart soars higher and higher
like a kite
As the two hearts soar,
they unite high up in the skies
I had no idea
that the melody of your love
would stir my heartstrings
Neither did I know
that you would traipse into my heart
and stay for ever
Come rain or shine,
not a moment shall we stay apart
Tied to the kite is a string's destiny
It soars higher and higher
The heart soars higher and higher
like a kite
This kite shall for ever be with you
It'll always be drawn to you
As the two hearts soar,
they unite high up in the skies
Higher and higher, they soar
I do
Hello?
It's me, sir. The groom
Remember me?
Yes. Tell me
I have information about Raees
Go on
A huge consignment of Raees
is arriving tomorrow, sir
If you bust it,
he'll be completely ruined
Good
All entry points to Gujarat are secured.
He can't breach it this time
No one leaves his post
until his truck is found
The swine will have to come out
to do business
This time he's a goner.
Check those trucks
Sadiqbhai, Majmudar has the whole
of Gujarat under surveillance
It's impossible to pass through
Let alone a truck,
not even a bottle can enter!
Majmudar is not going
to relax security soon
The swine's dead set against us
Indore Highway?
- Blocked
Umbergaon?
- Closed
Udaipur?
- No chance at all
We're in deep waters, Raees
Hey, turn around.
- No, Sadiq
We won't drown
We'll swim across
As shrewd as a merchant,
as fearless as a warrior!
Get him out.
Climb up and check
Miss Ratna was right
The coastline of Gujarat
is indeed the longest
Thanks for the help
I had heard
that Damla Seth rules the seas,
not the government
I witnessed it today.
- I've heard lots about you, too
It'll be fun to work together
God willing
He shook hands with Damla
If you want to save your business,
do something about Raees, Seth
Tomorrow is Muharram
He'll surely go to mourn
Majmudar is here!
I hope there's no trouble
Raees will handle it
Move
Do you know one Salim Shooter?
Well, he was murdered yesterday
Did you notice?
Or, were you mourning?
Pass it on
Kalupur goes
That's Taufiq Talli
Put some powder
And there you go!
And there goes your cover...
Sadiq
Your game's over
You'll go in on charges of murder
Don't worry about evidence.
I'll dig it out anyway
Arrest them.
- Sir
Bhai, the police picked up Four-eyes
in a murder case
Whose murder?
- Some Salim Shooter
Is Raja with you?
Yes, he is
Sir
You'll have to release Raees
Why?
He's confessing
that he killed Salim Shooter
So?
He's surrendering.
Arrest him
It's in writing, Majmudar.
Jai Hind!
May I ask you something?
How did you address your father?
Aunt!
Father. What else?
Hey!
What are you droning about father?
What is it?
Fine
Try this
What if someone calls you father?
Aasiya, who's going to call me father?
Hey! What are you doing?
Raees, I'll fall!
No! Raees, I'll fall!
Things will fall, Raees!
The phone's ringing!
- Yes. Pick it up
Here... pick it up
The phone!
- Yes, pick it up
Here
Hello?
- Raees, Musa here
Yes?
Jairaj hired the assassin to kill you
I give you Jairaj
O Laila
They call me Laila
Laila! That's me
I am
everyone's dream date
They call me Laila
Laila! That's me
I am
everyone's dream date
If I clap my eyes upon someone,
he is sure to be bewitched
He is completely floored
That's me! Laila
O Laila
These moments
are so enchanting
My eyes
are playing games with me
You are here
I can't believe my eyes
My heart
desires to feel you
They call me Laila
Laila! That's me
I am
everyone's dream date
O Laila
They call you Laila
That's you! Laila
You are
everyone's dream date
Sir, this is the beginning
of organised crime
If Raees isn't stopped now,
he'll burn the whole of Gujarat
After this terrible incident under
your jurisdiction, are you teaching me?
Now you give me in writing
why I shouldn't be transferring you!
You can transfer me anywhere
I won't spare Raees
You can take that in writing!
I've committed a crime, Aasiya!
After I was transferred out of Fatehpura,
Raees got an open field to play.
There was no stopping him
Raids were out of question
Because Raees would gift the police
a truckload of liquor every month
This month's stock
Convey our regards to Raeesbhai.
- Sure
No more bulldozers
Just cameras flashing
Officers posed for the cameras
and made the front pages of newspapers
with 'seized'liquor
The press, the police, the government,
all were a satisfied lot
Raees has sent shirts for you
See if the colour suits you
It's perfect.
Bye
There was one man
who could tilt the balance
Greetings, Pashabhai.
- The leader of the opposition
Raees wants to lend colour to your life
He sends a colour TV for you.
- Wow
But crafty as he was,
Raees won over everyone with cash
and consideration
Raees, you know the problem
with the mill
It can shut down anytime
We women must work to make ends meet
Help us, Raees
We want to buy sewing machines
and fend for ourselves
But the banks aren't giving us loans
Can you make bags?
Bags?
That's not a big deal
All right then,
I will give you sewing machines
Let me also place the order
for 10,000 bags right away
What will you do with so many bags?
Buy groceries for Aasiya?
I'll do what postman Hari does
Home delivery
God! So many phones!
Have you changed your business?
Are you selling phones now?
I'm not changing business.
These are for you
Now don't you complain
that I keep the phone busy!
Liar!
The day you do this for me,
pigs will fly!
No, I'm serious, Missus
From now on, Raees will be
at your service, round the clock
All you have to do is call and order
Sadiq...?
He is flattering you
He's come up with a novel idea.
Home delivery of liquor
Hey, Sadiq!
Why are you lying to her?
It's the truth.
- Truth, my foot!
Wait till you get married!
You'll know, wives are a terror
No, thanks. It's your problem.
- Don't yell at him!
Talk to me.
- He's fooling around. I was talking to you
Why did he have to butt in?
- Trying to flatter me, eh?
You think you are a charmer?
- No. Sadiq...
To heck with Sadiq!
- Sadiq, did you hear...?
Look at me
What did you say?
'I did this for you, I did that for you'
You did nothing for me. Ass!
Freaking Four-eyes!
Scared you, didn't I?
A bit
I pine for you
Don't torment me more, O cruel one
O cruel one
I'm drunk in your love
Don't intoxicate me more, O cruel one
O cruel one
Those eyes, mesmerising
Your words, alluring
I fall head over heels for you
a hundred times over
My heart
ceased to be mine,
ever since
I fell in love with you
You are the one who beats in my heart
Don't stir the heartstrings more,
O cruel one
Come close to me
Lend fragrance to my breath
Please do
Why should I alone express my love?
Why don't you express it, too?
Please do
You are going to kill me some day,
Your defence indeed is deadly
You are the beginning
You are the end
The story of my love is all about you
You are my leading light
Until death do us part,
O my cruel lover
Faizan
Jai Hind, sir!
Sir, sweets from Surat.
It's your favourite, isn't it?
What's up, Ramlal?
You're taking good care of me
Do you want leave?
- No, sir
It's a boy, sir
Congratulations!
What have you named him?
Faizan
For a Hindu father, you give your son
a Muslim name. Secularist, eh!
Not I, sir.
Raees has become a father
He has sent you an invite
Make sure you reply to him.
- Sir
He has become a father of a boy,
not the father of the nation
Give it back
It's my favourite
Remember those good old days?
We even stole Gandhiji's spectacles!
It was foolish, seriously.
- Your signal saved me that day, too
Else, he'd have thrashed me
You say it was foolish
but I did it out of Miss Ratna's fear
Fear? She was a terror!
Don't mention it to her now.
- We're here to give her the invite
She won't hit you for that
How did this happen?
Debt took his life
The mill shut down
The owner even refused compensation
He's gone!
'So what if five labourers die?'
'You will employ twenty-five more'
'to fill your coffers'
Bhimani Seth.
- What is it?
The labourers toiled for you for years.
You must give them
what is rightfully theirs.
- If you want rights, go to court
Why have you come here?
Get Deepak
Debt-ridden workers
are killing themselves
How will they pay for court cases?
Did I tell them to die?
Think it over
Done
I won't pay the labourers
You take something and back off
Before the movie ends,
the workers should get their money
Else, it'll be the end of you
Get that?
Place it here
Greetings, uncle.
- Bless you, dear
This is for Faizan,
from all the mill workers
Greetings.
- Greetings
Greetings
Isn't it beautiful?
It's really very beautiful
Why did you have to do this?
- It's not a gift, son
It's our blessings to you
You helped us get our money
and saved our families
This is the least we could do for Faizan
Thank you!
Jai Hind, sir
Why are you moving the vehicle
from the crime scene?
If the highway isn't cleared,
there'll be a traffic snarl, sir
We have to clear it, sir
Where was the truck headed to?
- Fatehpura, sir
Empty truck?
It was loaded with liquor, right?
Whose stuff was it?
Whose stuff?
Damla Seth's
Stop pimping. Do your duty.
Get it?
Get Damla.
- Sir
Jai Hind, sir
Sir, Damla Seth can't come.
- Why not?
He's away in Fatehpura
You may go.
- Sir
"Those drunken eyes"
"intoxicate me"
The Chief Minister, at Raees' party?
Mr Chief Minister!
- Sir... sir...
Raees!
- No politics today, please
How are you, sir?
- I'm fine
Give him a break!
There's ice-cream for everyone, guys.
- Okay, sir
Raees, he is Mr Hasmukh.
He is into construction
He executes all the government projects
I wanted you to meet him
You know Damla Seth
Aasiya, this is the CM.
- Hello
Let's have a drink
You drink like a fish here,
and in the parliament,
you take to sloganeering
'Ban liquor, save Gujarat'
Not in vain, sir
I believe in political agenda.
- I can see your political agenda
Elections are approaching.
Cut the opposition crap and join me
Mr CM!
The CM has bought a property
near Maninagar
He has assigned me to construct
a building. - Great
But the hitch is, it's occupied
Encroachers, you know.
And...
he wants your company
to get the place vacated
Can it be done?
Surely, if it's the CM's wish
I'll take 30 percent
Deal, Raees
You are right, sir
Damla is here with Raees
The Chief Minister and Pashabhai
are also here
You quit the city
but you haven't forgotten Raees
Can't help it
Raees and I share a strange relationship
We can't be together,
yet he won't let me go away
Cops! Run!
It's a raid!
Stop
Sit all of them up
Get him
Sit him up
Bro!
It's the cops!
Prohibition Act, section 66 and 67!
You are going in for ten years
Haul them in.
Bhagat!
Sir!
- Seize all the liquor
And seal the port.
- Sir!
Raees' lifeline and pipeline...
blow them out of the water!
Transfer Majmudar
to some godforsaken place, sir!
He is a constant pain in my neck
He's a police officer,
not a pawn I can play around with
He arrested Damla
Majmudar has started a fire in Kutch
The flames could torch me
and eventually reach you
If it isn't doused now,
everything will be razed
Sir?
Type a transfer order
Majmudar's?
Transfer him to the control room here.
He'll rot along with the old files
Sir
It happened, as usual
An official order, enclosed!
And I left, with bag and baggage
India is always losing!
By transferring me to the control room,
they thought I'd be like a snake,
defanged and harmless
But as they say,
it turned the tables!
Sir, we've got all the numbers
on Raees' home delivery lists
Tap them
Do you do home delivery?
- Yes. How many bottles?
New stock, sir.
- Two bottles, please
Only ten bottles?
Order hundred, sir.
Involuntarily, Raees pulled me
closer to him
From this spot,
I could hear his very heartbeat
From this point to that,
200 acres of land has been
transferred to you
You have made a huge investment
Your dream to make a housing colony,
'Our World' has finally come true
Raeesbhai,
this is the right time
to start the construction
Right
Start right away then
Fine
Bye, sir
Convey my regards to the CM.
- Bye
Did you hear about Pasha?
- I know
He's taking out a procession
to ban liquor
The swine has gone crazy
I'll fix him. Call him
Pasha here.
- Greetings, Pashabhai
A procession to ban liquor?
What's this new farce?
- Oh, come on, Raeesbhai
Elections are at hand
Besides, the liquor agenda
is my ticket to victory
This gimmick is inevitable.
- You know, Pasha,
your procession will hamper my business
Why don't we find a way out?
You find a way out,
I'll take the procession out
The procession will start from
the party office and go up to Gotri
Okay
Pasha here.
- At least,
change the route
Don't lead it through my territory.
- Impossible
The road to my vote bank
runs through your neighbourhood
Do as you please.
The procession will pass through
What now?
- Get this clear, Pasha
If this procession takes off,
it will be your final journey
How about some tea?
Did you send for me, sir?
- Yes, Popat
Hot news
Before it cools down,
break it to the press
'Raees issues an open threat'
'If Pasha takes out a procession,
it will be his final journey'
You torched his castle,
and he has no idea what hit him!
Do it and watch the fun
Right, sir
And the circus begins!
'Raees' open threat: If Pasha takes out
a procession, it will be his final journey'
Hello?
- Are you crazy
to issue an open challenge in the media?
I didn't speak to the press.
Pasha has dug his own grave
I told you not to make a fuss.
Just sell liquor. Leave politics to me
Hang up!
Shutters down!
Keep your vehicles off the road!
The procession is coming this way.
Please maintain peace!
Are you ready?
- Yes, we are!
Let's see who is man enough
to stop this procession!
Who is man enough?
It's the call of Gujarat!
- Victory to Pashabhai!
Close the shops!
Deploy the barricades!
Keep people off!
The procession is passing through
Raees' neighbourhood
Situation under control.
- Copy
Down with the government!
Let's see who is man enough
to stop Pashabhai's procession!
Let's see who is man enough!
It's the call of Gujarat!
- Victory to Pashabhai!
To war!
Turn around!
Go!
Hack him!
Start shelling!
Fire!
I warned you
not to pass through my neighbourhood
It hampers my business
Now you know
who is man enough!
Who's the real man!
Swine!
Raees lived up to his challenge.
What action will you take now?
Look, we...
- Swati Trivedi, Maha Gujarat Times
Raees is your friend
while Pashabhai is your rival
Did Raees act on your orders?
- Gujarat politics hasn't stooped so low
The police are doing their job.
- You don't let the police do their job
Are Majmudar's frequent transfers
due to your proximity with Raees?
Raees will be in jail
within the next 24 hours
Is that a promise, Mr CM?
- Sir!
Yes? Go on
Why should I go to jail?
Send Pasha to jail.
He created all the mess
What about my business?
I'll give you
all the facilities in jail
Do your business from jail.
Who stops you?
Oh, really?
I'll have you released when you tell me
It's only a matter of a few days
Is that a promise?
- I'm with you
Don't worry
Greetings, bhai.
- Greetings
Hello? Who is it?
- It's me
At this hour? Is all well?
I'm missing you
Liar
Listen.
We made 22,000 in cash today
That's not what I called you for
I told you,
I'm missing you
Really?
Really? Only 22,000?
Darn it!
Freaking duffer!
Business meant life to you
And finally, they traded you
Pasha and the Chief Minister
have joined hands. Take a look
'Coalition politics
completely wipes out Raees'
I told you
to get used to tea at the cop station
Get ready to contest the elections
Raees, politics is not meant for us.
I'm arranging bail for you
The winds blow south, Sadiq
To be free again,
I must win the elections
Is it easy to win elections?
We'll need votes as well as cash
You organise the cash
I'll garner the votes
Raees has done a lot for the people
We'll surely win the elections
Listen carefully!
He is Raees
He's a class apart
Love him, and he'd even give up
his life for you
Act smart,
and you'll see the worst of him
That's Raees
He's as fearless as a warrior
and as shrewd as a merchant
As cool as a cucumber
yet as fierce as fire
Right or wrong,
business is his faith
Business is his first love
That's Raees
He is Raees
He's a class apart
Bail granted
Raees registers an historical victory
in Fatehpura
None of his rivals
could even save his deposit
That's Raees
The name's Raees
He is Raees
He's a class apart
I told you, you'd be the first
to see Our World when I make it
I'll show you today.
- Really?
Look
Over here
In a straight line, on both sides,
tall houses are standing
Children are flying kites on the roof
The sky is enveloped with kites
And...
over there... no, right behind you,
there's an English-medium school
Children are speaking fluent English
Good morning, Miss Ratna
Here...
a hospital in memory of my mother
The Parsi doctor will be in-charge
I'm sure he'll still charge only 2 rupees
Aasiya, the air will be rich
with everything here
There will be no fear of starvation
or the curse of poverty
The mornings will be spent feasting
while the nights in celebration
Amen
It's a fantastic scheme, Raees
Right, friends?
- Of course
But the amount is too big for all of us
Qasim, who is asking
for the entire amount?
You don't need to pay
the entire amount now
You have to pay only half the amount
And the rest in ten years
You can pay in monthly instalments
for the next ten years
Is ten years too short a period?
Don't worry, don't be apprehensive
I guarantee you. This is
my neighbourhood, you are my people
You own your house
from the very first day
All of you will get the deeds
of agreement. I guarantee you that
Your word is final.
Let's do it
'Our World'
Greetings
Mr Majmudar!
It's been so long
Tell me. Are you here to meet me
or to conduct a raid?
Well, rest assured.
Everything is legal about Our World
Liquor pays for the construction.
What could be more legal?
Luck favours you these days
Days and nights are meant
for people, Mr Majmudar
Lions rule for ages
Try tea from Our World.
Come here, kid
It might change your perception.
Cheers
To me, you are still the same
I have changed a bit, Mr Majmudar
You can't tap this politician's phones now.
- No, no
I don't need to listen
to your phones anymore
I'm here as the Superintendant
of Police, Crime
Trust me,
I had no hand in your transfer this time
Honestly
I know
All your hands are tied
That's why
I came here to reason with you
Make sure you don't give me an opportunity
Never.
I never gave you one
Hang on, SP
If you say, here, in Our World,
I'll book an apartment for you
I'll book a place for you
in my world
He won the elections yesterday,
and today he is building Our World
Raees is going to become a messiah!
- Sir,
you have an urgent call from Delhi
Yes?
What?
Turn on the TV.
- Sure
Yes, sir?
In Uttar Pradesh,
rioters targeted a train
carrying passengers returning from Hajj
Several people are being reported killed
The incident has provoked communal riots
in many parts of the country
Police have imposed indefinite curfew
in several districts
I don't want riots in my city.
You will handle Zone 1, Shambu
Zone 2 is the most sensitive
Majmudar, you will take charge there.
- Sir
Ten days of curfew has brought
the entire State to a standstill
People have little access
to food, water, milk or medicines
Give this to aunt Laxmi.
- Sure
Listen.
This is for Dulari's baby
Deliver the bottle of milk to her
right away
Distribute the meals in police vans
Raees sends food for all of you.
- Raees! God bless you!
The children have been starving.
- Easy
Why don't you answer the calls?
- Creditors are calling up
The construction guys
and the grocers
Why aren't the bottles delivered yet?
Can't help it.
No orders due to curfew
Don't mind this. But you must either stop
the construction work for some time
or the free meals.
- No way
I can't do that.
- Sign here
Stop free meals to the Hindu colony.
It'll ease the burden
Hey!
Did you ever consider religion
while doing business?
None should starve to death.
Neither Hindu nor Muslim
They are our people
Neither the free meals will stop
nor the construction of Our World
I'll organise the money
Stop the meals, my foot!
Mr CM, I agree
you have the riots under control
You must control Raees now
His Our World
is becoming everyone's world
It will be no one's!
Those who are buying Raees' dream
will soon grab his throat
I'll make a pauper out of that king
in a trice!
I'm putting that site in the green zone
How much money do we have?
- About 200,000
That's all?
Have you swallowed the rest?
What are you saying, Raees?
- Don't interfere!
I'm talking business here
He should have the accounts.
Tell me
What?
- Give me the accounts
You want accounts?
Accounts of what?
The money spent on the elections?
Or, the money spent on acres of land
for Our World?
Since the last three weeks, we've been
distributing free meals to four colonies
It doesn't come for free!
I swallowed it?
He's asking me the accounts!
Don't you yell at me!
Are you doing me a favour
by giving me the details?
I've been noticing.
You get worked up over every little thing
What is wrong with you?
He isn't annoyed over the money
but over the CM
The CM put our land in the green zone
So what?
The deeds are in our names, right?
- He changed the law
No construction can be done there.
Only farming
What happens to Our World?
People's houses, money...?
The money's gone!
Everything has fallen apart, Aasiya
How can it fall apart just like that?
There must be a way
Think.
Talk to the CM
He might understand...
- Cut the crap!
No need to use your brains
I don't need anyone's advice!
Go on, get back to work
Go!
What good is yelling?
Will it get our money back?
Or, will it help build the colony?
To heck with the colony!
- Hey! Raees!
Stop it, Raees!
- Shut her up!
Move, Sadiq
Raees
Tell everyone the truth
Or, assure them
that everything will be fine
It will be
For God's sake...
For God's sake, leave me alone!
That's it!
Aasiya
At the crossroads
of life and death,
I find myself today!
O Destiny, I thought you were a friend
And I walked on,
in your footsteps,
latching on to you,
holding you dear!
Yet, you compelled me
to do things
I'd never have done otherwise!
We could never understand
each other
I'm tired, Aasiya!
Greetings, Raeesbhai.
- Greetings
Bhai,
Four-eyes is here
He's up to his neck in debt
I know
Nawab, what about our Doha delivery?
The cops are very active, bhai
Haji, Ejaz, Haribhai,
everyone has refused
Let Raees in
Send him in.
- Go on
Greetings, bhai.
- Tell me
Can I help you?
I need a small loan, bhai
In fact, you need a huge amount
Trust me, bhai
I'll repay it,
with double the interest
I can't give you a loan
But I can put you on to something...
What about the Doha assignment?
Bhai, it's final.
Ejaz is delivering it
Stop him
The boys are already en route...
Don't worry, I'll handle him.
Put Raees on it
Bhai, listen to me...
Let Raees do the job
Gold is arriving from Doha,
to be delivered in Mumbai
I'll do it
The riots are over
but the curfew is still forced
How can we deliver it?
- Sadiq,
if we can avoid curfew and reach Mumbai,
so can the gold. We can do it
Think over it.
If you can do it, fine
Ejaz is on it anyway.
- No, we'll do it
Sure?
- Sure
Give him the money
Thank you, bhai
Sir!
What's this?
- I hope it's not drugs
No.
- Nope
It's only the packaging
You have all the gold there
Is the gold there?
- Yes
Let it pass then
Bhairu!
Inform Raees that his truck has left.
- Okay, sir
Will it be tea or booze?
Booze... in a teacup!
No one's losing his money
on Our World, Sadiq
We'll repay everyone
God willing!
Today, in a series of explosions,
five blasts
rocked three metropolitan cities
of North India
People were hauling the injured
to the hospital in cars and scooters
That's when we realised
the intensity of the blasts
We can identify the body
only if it is intact,
not if it is blown to pieces
A wave of fright and anger
has swept the entire country
No organisation has taken responsibility
for the blasts yet
The explosions are linked to Gujarat
The explosive used was smuggled in
through the waters of Gujarat
I have no idea, sir.
I'm just a driver!
All I do is deliver the goods
Where did you pick up the stuff from?
From Porbandar, sir
I know nothing, sir!
Whose stuff was it?
Damla Seth and Nawab smuggled it in
On whose orders?
Raees'
Hello?
- It's a terrible mess-up, Raees
The packaging materials
with Musa's gold weren't plastic
They were RDX bombs!
Bombs?
How can they be bombs?
If they were bombs,
couldn't the officer detect them?
RDX is a new type of bomb
They were used for these explosions
The swine Musa betrayed us!
Raees, this time the cops won't arrest us,
they will shoot us down!
Get out of there.
See you when I see you
Good God!
God!
I had no idea what I was doing!
Raees
In trying to save my people,
I've burned down the entire city, Aasiya!
Good God!
I've burned down the city!
Run! Run!
There are no eyewitnesses to place Raees
on the port, sir
Damla shot himself,
while Nawab is absconding
We can never prove it in court.
- Let the court do its job, Majmudar
You go and arrest him
He's a master at destroying evidence.
Last time he was jailed,
he came out a politician.
God knows what he'll try this time
Even I want Raees, sir
To maintain peace,
war is a must this time, sir
I can't give what you seek
in writing, Majmudar
Let's go
Who wants it in writing anyway?
The cops will be here any moment.
Run, Raees!
I won't run
I'm not a coward, Sadiq!
I'm not!
You are innocent.
And to prove that, you should live
If you don't escape, they will...
kill you!
Sadiq is right
Get out of here, please!
- No!
If I escape, the cops
will make life miserable for you
Reason with her, Sadiq
Take Faizan and Aasiya to Sanjanwala's
Now. Right now!
You know that
it's the only safest place for them
And you?
- You know that, Sadiq
I'm not going anywhere without you.
- Don't argue with me!
Period!
Aasiya, trust me
I'll fix everything
But right now,
this is the right thing to do
But...
I won't run
I don't know, sir!
You can break our bodies
but not our resolve!
Pick up the swine's family!
- We are innocent!
Please let us go!
- Find each one of them!
Where's Raees?
Thrash all of them
till you find Raees!
He's a brother to me!
I'll charge all of you under
the Terrorist Act! - Raees...
was our only support during our bad times!
Raees is here
Send him in.
And listen
Take his gun
Okay
What news?
- Raees has gone underground
But Sadiq is at Sanjanwala's.
- Find Raees. Yes, Devji?
We found Nawab
Make preparations.
- Sir
Now!
- Listen up!
You betrayed me, Musa
You made me smuggle in bombs
in the name of gold
You have done a noble deed.
You will be blessed with heaven
Killing innocents
doesn't lead one to heaven, Musa
Raees, listen to me
I'm going to Doha
Come with me.
We'll be safe out there
I'm going nowhere
I'm not letting anyone go either.
- Kill Four-eyes!
Raees!
Innocents were killed, Musa
My principles were laid to waste
in no time
I'm a businessman
But I don't trade in religion
One last thing
Never call me Four-eyes!
Hello?
- Doctor,
let me speak to Sadiq
It's Raees
Sadiq here.
- I've set everything right, Sadiq
Are you all right?
We are fine
Are the cops there?
No... Bhaijaan!
Okay
I'm coming
Come, Bhaijaan
Who called?
It was Raees, right?
Why did you call him here, Sadiq?
What are you going to do with Raees?
I just want to chat with him.
Take her away
He is a businessman, sir.
He never betrayed anyone
Do not be unfair to him, Mr Majmudar!
Devji...
- Sir?
Shoot him at sight.
- Sir!
One bad decision has brought upon
a great calamity!
But I won't let anyone come to harm
They are innocent
I alone am at fault
Pray that we meet soon
I'm coming, Ammi
Sir, a van is headed
towards the doctor's house
How many people are in the van?
- No idea
Is Raees inside?
- It's hard to see
Target all the doors of the van.
Shoot on suspicion
It could be Raees' ploy
The van stopped at the gate
Brace up for every situation.
Anything can happen
He is getting off, sir.
- Shoot!
I'll answer my superiors.
Shoot!
Raees is not alone, sir!
- He's brought the press along!
What?
- Yes, sir. A van full of reporters
Shall I shoot, sir?
- Hold your fire!
I repeat, hold your fire.
No one shoots!
Guns down!
Back off!
Fall back!
Fall back, will you?
Hold them back
Move it!
Bhaijaan, eh!
Hold them back
Enough of the adoration!
Let's go
Take care.
- Take him away
When you knew
how this was going to end for you,
why did you return?
Would you have spared my people
if I didn't?
I had to return to save my flesh and blood
But what you are about to do,
Mr Majmudar...!
Well?
What happened?
You don't trust the system anymore?
Or, yourself?
Both, perhaps
Can you live with my blood
on your hands, Mr Majmudar?
Give these to my wife
and tell her the truth
I promised her
that I won't run
I feel
this is the perfect distance
to shoot, Mr Majmudar
What say?
Turn around, Raees
Not in the back
Shoot me in the front, sir
I can.
You know that
Shoot
Is it true that no business is small?
And no faith greater than business?
It's true
As long as it doesn't harm anyone
Bhaijaan!
What if someone calls you father?
The mornings will be spent feasting
while the nights in celebration
Amen
In trying to save my people,
I've burned down the entire city!
I'm not sure if I was right or wrong then
But Raees' words
ring in my ears even today
Can you live with my blood
on your hands, Mr Majmudar?